<dictionary>
<url>http://www.kevyb.com/gettinghitched</url>
<share>
<text>
You are invited to Kristin and Matthew's wedding party!
</text>
<facebook></facebook>
<twitter></twitter>
</share>
<ui>
<label_close>
<![CDATA[ close ]]>
</label_close>
</ui>
<cookie>
<body>
<![CDATA[
We use cookies to give you the best possible experience on our website. Our cookies don't collect personal information. Click the <button class="cookie__btn-more">cookie</button> to read more and how to manage your cookie settings. <button class="cookie__btn-accept">close</button>
]]>
</body>
</cookie>
<loader>
<label_loading>
<![CDATA[ PARTY!!! ]]>
</label_loading>
</loader>
<intro>
<text>
<![CDATA[
<span class="intro__text intro__text--blue">Friends and Family!!!<br></span><span class="intro__text intro__text--pink">You are invited...<br/></span><span class="intro__text intro__text--green">^1000<br/></span><span class="intro__text intro__text--green">to Kristin and Matthew's<br/>wedding<br>clambake<br>dance party!!!!</span>
]]>
</text>
</intro>
<editor>
<label_function>
<![CDATA[ Information ]]>
</label_function>
<label_apply>
<![CDATA[ YEP! ]]>
</label_apply>
<label_reset>
<![CDATA[ Begin Again? ]]>
</label_reset>
<label_bracket>
<![CDATA[ } ]]>
</label_bracket>
</editor>
<reset>
<label_heading>
<![CDATA[ Begin again? ]]>
</label_heading>
<label_cancel>
<![CDATA[ Nope! ]]>
</label_cancel>
<label_reset>
<![CDATA[ Yup! ]]>
</label_reset>
</reset>
<info>
<booking_url>
<![CDATA[ http://www.kevyb.com/gettinghitched ]]>
</booking_url>
<section>
<title> Who?</title>
<in_nav>true</in_nav>
<id>1</id>
<body>
<![CDATA[
<p><span class="pink">Kristin Grace Erickson and Matthew Patrick Galvin...</span></p><p><img src="images/weddingpic2.jpg" width=500/></p>
]]>
</body>
</section>
<section>
<title> What?</title>
<in_nav>true</in_nav>
<id>2</id>
<body>
<![CDATA[
<span class="blue">...are getting married and want to celebrate with you! </span><br><br>
<span class="green">Please dress for a casual outdoor garden party featuring croquet, rowdy kids, team trivia, live music, dancing, cake, and cocktail-style Cape Cod cuisine.</span><br><br>
<span class="orange">The party will be at the Galvin family compound in Cotuit, Cape Cod.</span><br><br>
<p><img src="images/cotuitHouse.jpg" width=500/></p>


]]>
</body>
</section>
<section>
<title> When?</title>
<in_nav>true</in_nav>
<id>3</id>
<body>
<![CDATA[
<span class="orange">The party will be on Thursday, July 28th, 2016 at 3pm.</span><br><br>
<span class="green">It'll be high season on the Cape, so please make your arrangements soon.</span><br><br>
<span class="pink">The following websites may be helpful for finding accommodations:</span><br><br>
<p><ul>
		<li class="blue"><u><a href="http://www.thesantuitinn.com/" class="blue">The Santuit Inn</a></u></span><br><br></li>
		<li><span class="orange"><u><a href="http://www.seamistcapecod.com/" class="orange">Sea Mist Resort, Cape Cod</a></u></span><br><br></li>
		<li><span class="green"><u><a href="http://www.vrbo.com/" class="green">VRBO.com - Vacation Rentals By Owner</a></u></span><br><br></li>
		<li><span class="pink"><u><a href="http://www.airbnb.com/" class="pink">airbnb.com</a></u></span></li>
</ul></p>
]]>
</body>
</section>
<section>
<title> Where?</title>
<in_nav>true</in_nav>
<id>4</id>
<body>
<![CDATA[
<p><span class="green">1698 Santuit-Newtown Rd, Barnstable, MA 02635</span></p><iframe src="https://www.google.com/maps/embed?pb=!1m18!1m12!1m3!1d2981.837952816737!2d-70.44784268468341!3d41.637633988407245!2m3!1f0!2f0!3f0!3m2!1i1024!2i768!4f13.1!3m3!1m2!1s0x89e4cd59a45000eb%3A0x678a2eed6fa41165!2s1698+Santuit-Newtown+Rd%2C+Barnstable%2C+MA+02635!5e0!3m2!1sen!2sus!4v1463879749118" width="600" height="450" frameborder="0" style="border:0" allowfullscreen></iframe>
]]>
</body>
</section>
<section>
<title> R.S.V.P.</title>
<in_nav>true</in_nav>
<id>5</id>
<color>green</color>
<body>
<![CDATA[
<iframe src="https://docs.google.com/forms/d/1KX96IpoZLjRWjooLjC9sYJgKYZHxwpKUfkAhSTkV9Ug/viewform?embedded=true" width="550" height="500" frameborder="0" marginheight="0" marginwidth="0">Loading...</iframe>
]]>
</body>
</section>
<section>
<title>Terms of use</title>
<in_nav>false</in_nav>
<id>6</id>
<color>pink</color>
<body>
<![CDATA[
<h1 class="orange"><span aria-hidden="true">&lt;</span>PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS SITE</h1> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Terms of website use</h2> <p class="blue">These terms of use (together with the documents referred to in it) set out the terms that apply when you use our website www.barclayscodeplayground.co.uk ("our site"), whether as a guest or a registered user. Use of our site includes accessing, browsing, or registering to use it.</p> <p class="lightgreen shifted">Please read these terms of use carefully before you start to use our site, as these will apply to your use of our site. We recommend that you print a copy of these terms for future reference.</p> <p class="blue shifted">By using our site, you confirm that you accept these terms of use and that you agree to comply with them. If you do not agree to these terms of use, you must not use our site.</p> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Information about us</h2> <p class="blue">www.barclayscodeplayground.co.uk is a site operated by Barclays Bank PLC("we", “us” or “our”). We are registered in England and Wales under company number 1026167 and have our registered office at 1 Churchill Place, London E14 5HP. Barclays Bank PLC is authorised by the Prudential Regulation Authority and regulated by the Financial Conduct Authority (Financial Services Register number: 122702).</p> <h1 class="orange"><span aria-hidden="true">&lt;</span>DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU</h1> <p class="lightgreen">We do not collect any personal data from you.</p> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Changes to these terms</h2> <p class="blue">We reserve the right to revise these terms at any time without notice by amending this page. Your continued access to or use of this site will constitute your acceptance of such changes. Please check this page from time to time to take notice of any changes we make, as they are binding on you.</p> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Changes to our site</h2> <p class="blue">We may update our site from time to time, and may change the content at any time. We do not guarantee that our site, or any content on it, will be free from errors or omissions.</p> <p class="lightgreen shifted">Although we have taken all reasonable care to ensure that the information provided on this site is accurate, we make no representations, warranties or guarantees, whether express or implied, that the content on our site is accurate, complete or up-to-date.</p> <p class="blue shifted">Opinions and any other contents at the site are provided by us for personal use and informational purposes only and are subject to change without notice.</p> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Accessing our site</h2> <p class="blue">We do not guarantee that our site, or any content on it, will always be available or uninterrupted or error free. We do not guarantee that our site will be secure or free from bugs or viruses. Access to our site is permitted on a temporary basis. We may in our sole discretion suspend, withdraw, discontinue or change all or any part of our site without notice, including without limitation where we believe that you have not acted in accordance with the terms and conditions of our site. We will not be liable to you if for any reason our site is unavailable at any time or for any period.</p> <p class="lightgreen shifted">You are responsible for making all arrangements necessary for you to have access to our site. You are also responsible for ensuring that all persons who access our site through your internet connection are aware of these terms of use and other applicable terms and conditions, and that they comply with them.</p> <h2 class="pink">Intellectual property rights</h2> <p class="blue">The entire content of this site is subject to copyright with all rights reserved and the information held is for your personal use only. You may not download (all or in part), transmit or modify the site without our prior permission. However, you may print out part or all of the site for your own personal use. You must not use any part of the content on our site for commercial purposes without obtaining a licence to do so from us or our licensors . We are the owner or the licensee of all intellectual property rights in our site, and in the material published on it. Those works are protected by copyright laws and treaties around the world. All such rights are reserved.</p> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Limitation of our liability</h2> <p class="blue">We will accept no liability in any event including (without limitation) negligence for any damages or loss of any kind, including (without limitation) direct, indirect, incidental, special or consequential damages, expenses or losses arising out of, or in connection with your use or inability to use the Site, or in connection with any error, omission, defect, computer virus or system failure, or loss of any profit, goodwill or reputation, even if expressly advised of the possibility of such loss or damages, arising out of or in connection with the access of, use of, performance of, browsing in or linking to other sites from this site.</p> <p class="lightgreen shifted">Nothing in these terms of use excludes or limits our liability for death or personal injury arising from our negligence, or our fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation, or any other liability that cannot be excluded or limited by English law.</p> <p class="blue shifted">We reserve the right to modify, suspend or discontinue, temporarily or permanently, the site or any part of it, with or without notice, at any time. You agree that we shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any such modification, suspension or discontinuance of the site.</p> <h1 class="orange"><span aria-hidden="true">&lt;</span>THIRD PARTY SITES</h1> <p class="blue">Some of the content on this site is provided by third party providers and we assume no responsibility for the accuracy of such content.</p> <p class="lightgreen shifted">Any links to third party internet websites from this site should not be interpreted as an endorsement by us of those websites. You use such links entirely at your own risk and we accept no responsibility or liability for the content, use or availability of such websites. We have not verified the truth or accuracy of any content of such websites. You are responsible for compliance with any third party terms relating to your use of those websites.</p> <p class="blue shifted">No third party is permitted to link any other website to this site without obtaining our prior written consent.</p> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Applicable law</h2> <p class="blue">These terms of use (and any non-contractual disputes or claims) are governed by English law. We both agree to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of England and Wales to determine any matter or dispute in connection with or arising out of this site and these terms and conditions.</p> <p class="lightgreen shifted">This site is designed for use in the UK and is not directed to, nor intended for distribution or use by, any person or entity in any jurisdiction or country where the publication or availability of this site or such distribution or use would be contrary to local law or regulation. If you choose to access information on this site, it is your responsibility to comply with the applicable local, national or international laws and any use of this site outside the UK is entirely at your own risk. For guidance relating to your specific situation, please contact your legal adviser.</p> <h2 class="pink"><span aria-hidden="true">&gt;</span>Contact us</h2> <p class="blue">To contact us, please call at: 0800 400 100</p> <p class="orange">Thank you for visiting our site.</p> <p><img src="images/logo-barclays.jpg" alt="Barclays logo"/></p>
]]>
</body>
</section>
</info>
</dictionary>
